AHMED ALI HASSAN

Address: Giza, Egypt. **Mobile**: (+20) 01142812345

Email: ahmed.ali.hassan108@gmail.com
Linked In: www.linkedin.com/in/ahmed-ali-993011215/

Objective

Energetic and optimistic with 2 years of professional experience assisting clients in solving their issues, , and I'm seeking a challenging position in your company where I can achieve high rates of client satisfaction to the company and develop my technical and interpersonal skills.

Education

Faculty of Law – Cairo University

2014 - 2018

Bachelor's degree in Law

Experience

El Nasr Casting Company

Apr2023 – May2023

IT Help Desk Trainee

• Networking · OS · Hardware · Software · Troubleshooting

Sami el-sayed, law office

Oct 2020 - Aug 2022

Lawyer

- Prepares legal documents and contracts
- Represents clients of the office in court
- Renders legal advice to clients of the office
- Real estate registration
- corporate law

El halwany, law office

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020

Lawyer

- Prepares legal documents and contracts
- Represents clients of the office in court
- Renders legal advice to clients of the office

Arma Trading

Jan 2019 – Aug 2019

Coordintor

- Prepares daily reports
- Products marketing

Courses

- Russian Cultural Center, Certified, English course; (level 12)
- Human resources and development;
- IT Support Professional ,Google:
 - -Technical Support Fundamentals Certificate;
 - Computer Networking Certificate;
 - -Operating Systems Certificate;
 - -System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services Certificate;
- Programming Foundations: Beyond the Fundamentals ,Linkedin
- Programming Foundations: Fundamentals ,Linkedin

Languages

English: Advanced

Arabic: Native

Hard Skills

• Microsoft Office;

• Photoshop;

• HTML5&CSS3;

Soft Skills

• Leadership, Marketing Skills, Selling Skills, Problem Solving, Communication Skills, Negotiation Skills, Decision-making, Self Study, Time management, Attention to detail, Creativity, Multitasking,

Additional Information

- Military Service Status: Exempt
- Date of Birth: 10/2/1996

Reference

Upon request